Stephanie Unger

Digital marketing professional with excellence in project management and content development

468 Newton Ave, Oakland, CA 94606 | Stephanie@ungermail.com | 352.672.1026

Qualifications Summary

Experienced project manager and freelance writer with professional interests in social media marketing, business development, and arts administration. Knowledgeable of project and personnel management, marketing campaign strategies, branding solutions, and technical and expository writing. Motivational and empowering team leader who provides constructive criticism and effective direction. Successful in educating team members to realize their full potential to create unique digital content, relationships and customer experiences.

Core Competencies

Technical and Creative Writing • Blogging • Digital Media Content Creation • Marketing Content Creation • Proofreading & Editing • Web & Data Analytics • Search Engine Optimization • Social Media Optimization • Leadership • Business Administration & Management • Business Development • Account Management • Customer Care • Brand Management • Basic Graphic Design

Technical Skills

- Social Media Facebook, Twitter, Instagram, Pinterest, LinkedIn, Google+, Sprout Social, Rignite, Buffer
- Applications MS Office (Word, Excel), Apple Pages, Canva
- Project Management Asana
- Web Development WordPress

Relevant Professional Experience

BeatCreative Marketing / Orlando, FL (remote) / December 2013-October 2015 Social Media Project Manager

Managed projects for up to 10 clients.

Developed marketing content for up to 5 clients at a time.

Lead a team of 5-7 people (writers, administration, and interns).

Awarded 1st place for event social media by Florida Festivals and Events Association.

Wrote the entry that awarded company founder "Changemaker 2015" by MeetingsNet.

Remilon, LLC / Mountain View, CA (remote) / May 2013-September 2013

Content Writer (Contract)

Created content for Education-Portal.com.

Innervation Dance Cooperative / Chicago, IL / October 2010-September 2013

Media Director, Touring and Outreach Director

Helped coordinate grant writing for a city-wide grant that awarded dancer pay for a year.

Oversaw dance company of 25+ people.

Coordinated tour performances for 20+ school shows for 2012-2013.

Developed website content and wrote quarterly newsletters.

Assisted with planning quarterly fundraising events and annual gala.

Russian Pointe / Chicago, IL / December 2008-October 2010

Business Development

Assisted development of ground-breaking marketing materials (video, book, and seminars).

Maintained business relationships with 200+ clients.

Brought in \$20,000+ in new business in 6 weeks (as interim New Business Manager).

Presented dozens of teaching seminars throughout the U.S. at industry trade shows and client locations.

Wrote articles for monthly newsletter.

Education

University of Florida, Gainesville, FL

Bachelors of Arts Degree in English, cum laude, 2006